Just one more day, just one more night Safe in
this warm and gentle light With you beside me, I
can't breathe Quiet promise, I believe This is
my home, this is my peace A fragile, temporary
lease On who I am, on who I'll be Before the
shadows come for me
An easy laugh A gentle sound On this familiar
sacred ground No need to guess No need to hide
With my true love right by my side A steady hand A
knowing glance A world away from happenstance
This is the truth I'm clinging to My sanctuary
here with you
Could I hear your footsteps in the hall? I
see your shadow on the wall. The air gets thick.
The silence screams. The end of all my fragile
dreams.
My heart begins to beat the drum For the cold
and silent man I must become
And now the mask comes down Just a face in a lonely
town The painted smile is in its place Leaving
not a single trace Of the boy I was a breath ago A
secret no one else can know The static's on, the
silence starts Protecting all my broken parts
The sacred smile
The static songs Can't let us see The fear in me A
silent start
A silent start